{
    "Questions": [
        {
            "name": "1",
            "question": "read and choose different kind of word",
            "type": "radio",
            "answer": "B",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "item": "A",
                    "content": "two"
                },
                {
                    "item": "B",
                    "content": "too"
                },
                {
                    "item": "C",
                    "content": "ten"
                },
                {
                    "item": "D",
                    "content": "seven"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "2",
            "question": "read and choose different kind of word",
            "type": "radio",
            "answer": "A",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "item": "A",
                    "content": "good"
                },
                {
                    "item": "B",
                    "content": "run"
                },
                {
                    "item": "C",
                    "content": "hop"
                },
                {
                    "item": "D",
                    "content": "swim"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "3",
            "question": "read and choose different kind of word",
            "type": "radio",
            "answer": "D",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "item": "A",
                    "content": "shirt"
                },
                {
                    "item": "B",
                    "content": "sweater"
                },
                {
                    "item": "C",
                    "content": "coat"
                },
                {
                    "item": "D",
                    "content": "cold"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "4",
            "question": "read and choose different kind of word",
            "type": "radio",
            "answer": "D",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "item": "A",
                    "content": "fly"
                },
                {
                    "item": "B",
                    "content": "bee"
                },
                {
                    "item": "C",
                    "content": "butterfly"
                },
                {
                    "item": "D",
                    "content": "rabbit"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "5",
            "question": "read and choose different kind of word",
            "type": "radio",
            "answer": "C",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "item": "A",
                    "content": "duck"
                },
                {
                    "item": "B",
                    "content": "elephant"
                },
                {
                    "item": "C",
                    "content": "pen"
                },
                {
                    "item": "D",
                    "content": "fox"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "6",
            "question": "The elephant ___ tall.",
            "type": "radio",
            "answer": "C",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "item": "A",
                    "content": "are"
                },
                {
                    "item": "B",
                    "content": "am"
                },
                {
                    "item": "C",
                    "content": "is"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "7",
            "question": "Ming can ___ a plane.",
            "type": "radio",
            "answer": "A",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "item": "A",
                    "content": "hear"
                },
                {
                    "item": "B",
                    "content": "feel"
                },
                {
                    "item": "C",
                    "content": "taste"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "8",
            "question": "Ming ___ hear a bird.",
            "type": "radio",
            "answer": "C",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "item": "A",
                    "content": "is"
                },
                {
                    "item": "B",
                    "content": "want to"
                },
                {
                    "item": "C",
                    "content": "can't"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "9",
            "question": "What color are the rabbits? --- _______.",
            "type": "radio",
            "answer": "C",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "item": "A",
                    "content": "It's white"
                },
                {
                    "item": "B",
                    "content": "They are lovely"
                },
                {
                    "item": "C",
                    "content": "They are white"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "10",
            "question": "Touch the doll. It's not rough. It's _______",
            "type": "radio",
            "answer": "C",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "item": "A",
                    "content": "soft"
                },
                {
                    "item": "B",
                    "content": "hard"
                },
                {
                    "item": "C",
                    "content": "smooth"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "11",
            "question": "Which of the following belongs to animals?",
            "type": "check",
            "answer": "BC",
            "choices": [
                {
                    "item": "A",
                    "content": "flower"
                },
                {
                    "item": "B",
                    "content": "elephant"
                },
                {
                    "item": "C",
                    "content": "fox"
                },
                {
                    "item": "D",
                    "content": "tree"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}